<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
    <name>XxHyde840xX's Choice Chops - Volume Three - FINAL CUT</name>
    <author>XxHyde840xX/Various</author>
	<url>https://github.com/XxHyde840xX/ChoiceChopsV3</url>
    <description>The final selection of choice items, carefully chopped from their respective mods. An exhaustive list is as follows;
	
[GrimWorld 40,000 - Vehicles of GrimWorld] - ONLY REQUIRES "VEHICLE FRAMEWORK" AND "VANILLA VEHICLES EXPANDED" MODS!
	
	- That's right folks, we've got MOAR TANKS BAYBEE! And I'm doing the heavy lifting to yeet a whole-ass framework out of the mix.
	- What I've done here is switched Research Prerequisites to Advanced Fabrication, and replaced references and build-costs where needed.
	- Nothing else really of note changed aside from the fact that you don't need the Core Imperialis mod to use these anymore. It was silly.
	- I plan to keep this all updated with any changes, fixes, and additions that happen to GrimWorld 40,000 Vehicles in the future.
	- Super incompatible with the original mod, which can be found here: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3026724919.
	
==================================================

[Apocrypha 2033 Apparel - Just The Sweats]
	
	- Who doesn't like a good comfy pair of sweats, amirite or amirite? So I chopped out some sweats from the Odz's Apocrypha 2033 mod.
	- You get a red pair, and a black pair, and a blue pair, and I've even gone to the trouble of making a brand new green pair.
	- Odz recently retired and disappeared from the modding scene to the best of my knowledge, and I wanted to preserve some of their stuff.
	- While I don't use the particular mod I grabbed the sweats from, the artwork is great, and you should check it out when you get a chance.
	- Definitely incompatible with the original mod, which can be found here: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2970206222.

==================================================

[WarCasket Barbatos Gundam Addon (Continued)] - REQUIRES "VANILLA FACTIONS EXPANDED: PIRATES" MOD!
	
	- Gotta toss one of my continuations into the mix here, and this one was an absolute pleasure to be able to put up on the Steam workshop.
	- There isn't much Gundam or mecha stuff on the workshop, and this WarCasket is an absolute beauty, brought forward from v1.3 of RimWorld.
	- The earlier version worked fine on v1.4 but I wanted to add some extra "oomph" for the contunuation so you're getting more bang for your buck.
	- I've increased the movement speed to +1.0c/s total with all 4 pieces equipped, and made it completely toxic resistant if you wear the whole set.
	- Woefully incompatible with the original mod and mine, which can be found at: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3038452790.
	
==================================================

[Amrita - Remastered]
	
	- I'm not quite sure if I'll ever get around to asking for permissions to release this one so I've included it here for your enjoyment.
	- Now you can both stop, and reverse the biological effects of aging on your pawns! Immortality on the Rim, realized! Awesome stuff.
	- I did take the liberty of adjusting the textures to reflect the ingredients required too make the stuff. No more pee-colored potions!
	- The wording on everything was ambiguous or straight-up confusing so I rewrote some things for clarity. And renamed the assembly.
	- Tragically incompatible with the original mod, which can be found here: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2349377017.

==================================================

[Stabilized Mechanites - Remastered]
	
	- Another mod I remastered for v1.4 that I'm not quite sure will ever be released on the workshop, so you get even more drugs to play with!
	- Back in business for v1.4 of RimWorld, and with a brand new color scheme and nifty new colored "inner-line" detail, these things POP now.
	- Again the wording on things was a little ambiguous so I rewrote a couple things and made some corrections where needed to clean things up.
	- Now you can give your colonists a stabilized version of the Fibrous and Sensory Mechanites diseases. C'mon, we both know those are a buff.
	- Shamefully incompatible with the original mod, which can be found here: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2813538784.

==================================================

[BDs Combat Enhancers - Remastered]
	
	- The final remaster for v1.4 of RimWorld, this one definitely didn't need too much, but you know me; I'm a sucker for Bill Doors.
	- As with most of the stuff I remaster, I've shifted the color of things a bit, corrected some spellingm or rewrote things for clarity.
	- The textures for these things were also obnoxiously large at 1280x1280. They're 512x512 now big but who's counting pixels? Not me...
	- Quixote says it's non-addictive. But it honestly might be? I'm not sure, the def is weird and it scares me. Lemme know if it is, will ya?
	- Chronically incompatible with the original mod, which can be found here: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2490784067.

==================================================

[RimField 5042 - Just The Tanks] - ONLY REQUIRES "VEHICLE FRAMEWORK" AND "VANILLA VEHICLES EXPANDED" MODS!
	
	- This is another mod I wanted to check out, but was disappointed at the required dependency for it since I don't use Aerocraft Framework.
	- So I disappeared the planes! Poof! Planes-B-Gone! Planes, no more! It was a shame since they were very pretty but sacrifices must be made.
	- You're getting a slick M1A5 and an EMKV90-TOR from Battlefield 2042 out of the deal to play with, so we're still eating good here. Promise.
	- As with the GrimWorld 40,000 vehicles mod, I will make sure to update this part of the mod with any changes, fixes, and additions in the future.
	- Emphatically incompatible with the original mod, which can be found here: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3031623119.
	
==================================================

[DF-101 "Kitsune" Armor and Helmet]
	
	- Hoo-boy, this one was an absolute pleasure, and an absolute pain to work on, but I think you're all gonna like what I've cooked up here.
	- It took some seriously strenuous color matching to get things just right, but the end result is something I'm weirdly proud of accomplishing.
	- Stats are comparable to marine armor from the Empire, but you'll get some extras with this one such as better insulation and some fun offsets.
	- SHOCKINGLY NOT INCOMPATIBLE WITH ANYTHING! Mods I've used for assets can be found by following the links below, make sure to check 'em out!
	- Assets Used: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2469449551 / https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3039182551.
	
=============================================================================================================================

This marks the end of this particular modpack, and the conclusion to the Choice Chops series. All good things must come to an end.

Just kidding! While technically the "Final Cut" of Choice Chops, I need an outlet for some of the stuff that won't ever see the light 
of day, save for my modlist and those of a few people who download some of the stuff on my github. There may come a time where I finally 
hang up my mod-butcher's apron, but until then, I hope you enjoy what I've compiled in the Choice Chops series. We eat good over here fam.
	  
	XxHyde840xX - o7
	  
=============================================================================================================================
|     This work is licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.      |
|              To view a copy of this license, visit http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/                      |
|                  or send a letter to Creative Commons, PO Box 1866, Mountain View, CA 94042, USA.                         |
=============================================================================================================================</description>
	<packageId>840.Choice.Chops.V3.FINALCUT</packageId>
		<supportedVersions>
			<li>1.4</li>
		</supportedVersions>
    <incompatibleWith>
		<li>Grimworld.Vehicles</li>
		<li>Odz.Apocrypha2033.Apparel</li>
		<li>Tach.GWarCasket</li>
		<li>840.Tach.GWarCasket</li>
		<li>y1nalin.amrita</li>
		<li>840.y1nalin.amrita</li>
		<li>SirVan.StabilizedMechanites</li>
		<li>840.SirVan.StabilizedMechanites</li>
		<li>3HSTltd.combat.enhancer</li>
		<li>840.3HSTltd.combat.enhancer</li>
		<li>MO.RimField5042</li>
		<li>840.MO.RimField5042</li>
	</incompatibleWith>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</packageId>
			<displayName>Royalty</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</packageId>
			<displayName>Ideology</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</packageId>
			<displayName>Biotech</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>SmashPhil.VehicleFramework</packageId>
			<displayName>Vehicle Framework</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3014915404</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaVehiclesExpanded</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Vehicles Expanded</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=3014906877</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VFE.Pirates</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Factions Expanded - Pirates</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2723801948</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>SmashPhil.VehicleFramework</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaVehiclesExpanded</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VFE.Pirates</li>
		<li>840.Choice.Chops</li>
		<li>840.Choice.Chops.V2</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>